// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is noun?",
    answer: "Represents a person, thing, or place",
    options: [
      "Represents a person, thing, or place",
      "Represents a person, thing, or place",
      "Represents a person, thing, or place",
      "Nothing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is verb?",
    answer: "describes an action",
    options: [
      "describes an name",
      "describes an action",
      "describes an person",
      "Nothing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is pronoun?",
    answer: "substitute for a noun",
    options: [
      "substitute for a adverb",
      "substitute for a interjection",
      "substitute for a noun",
      "Hometext Preprocessor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is adjective?",
    answer: "Describing",
    options: [
      "Describing",
      "Explaining",
      "Action",
      "Nothing"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is preposition?",
    answer: "shows how something is related to another word",
    options: [
      "shows how something is related to another person",
      "shows how something is related to another place",
      "shows how something is related to another word",
      "Nothing"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "conjunction",
  answer: "word that joins other words, phrases, clauses or sentences",
   options: [
    "word that joins other action",
    "word that joins other place",
    "word that joins other words, phrases, clauses or sentences",
    "option 4"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 7,
  question: "What is interjection",
  answer: "word that expresses emotion",
   options: [
    "word that expresses idea",
    "word that expresses workout",
    "word that expresses emotion",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 8,
  question: "What is Sentence",
  answer: "words that convey sense or meaning",
   options: [
    "For action",
    "For Design",
    "words that convey sense or meaning",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 9,
  question: "What is team",
  answer: "Consist of 2 ord more",
   options: [
    "Consist of 2 ord more",
    "Consist of 1",
    "Both Option 1 & 2",
    "Nothing"
  ]
 },
 {
  numb: 10,
  question: "Give 1 example of Hygiene kit",
  answer: "Toothbrush",
   options: [
    "wood",
    "spoon",
    "Toothbrush",
    "Nothings"
   ]
 },
];
